<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic-6414" xml:lang="en-us" class="- topic/topic "><title class="- topic/title ">Cellar Restaurant</title><shortdesc class="- topic/shortdesc ">Come to the Cellar, a casual Greek-American place with a variety of cuisine in a relaxed environment with a lodgelike feel.</shortdesc><body class="- topic/body "><p class="- topic/p ">Located in downtown Blacksburg, the Cellar Restaurant (the Cellar, as we like to call it) is a fun place to meet up with friends, family, or other loved ones--I know because I have, just as I'm guessing you have as well. Known for its wide selection of beers and a basement bar, this spot is unique. Opening in 1929, the Cellar is Blacksburg's oldest bar. The restaurant and bar moved upstairs in 1990, but the original downstairs bar remains mostly unchanged since 1963. With its chill, rustic atmosphere and warm, inviting ambiance, this place is definitely a favorite of mine. One of my favorite things I remember getting from there is the Chicken Pesto Pie, which is one of their signature baked pizzas  topped with chicken, red onions, and red bell peppers, and swapping out their red sauce for a pesto sauce. I certainly plan to go back to it!</p><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">Out front of the Cellar</title><image href="images/thecellaroutside.jpg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">Photo showing the view of the Cellar from out front of the restaurant, with people sitting out front on the patio eating and talking.</alt></image></fig><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">Inside the Cellar</title><image href="images/thecellarinside.jpg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">Photo showing inside of the Cellar, with chairs and tables scattered throughout the room. There is a bar at the back of the room, with black chairs lining the counter to it. The overall vibe is a friendly, rustic one that really makes you feel welcome.</alt></image></fig></body></topic>