<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic-8935" xml:lang="en-us" class="- topic/topic "><title class="- topic/title ">Mellow Mushroom</title><shortdesc class="- topic/shortdesc ">Visit this funky, art-filled chain pizzeria featuring craft beer, calzones &amp; creative stone-baked pizzas located in the heart of downtown Blacksburg.</shortdesc><body class="- topic/body "><p class="- topic/p ">Known for their artsy vibe inspired by the 1970s, Mellow Mushroom has become a crowd favorite, as well as mine. They have a vast assortment of specialty pizzas that are fun to try. But if you are set on paving your own path and would like to create your own pizza, they have a build-your-own option as well. They have their own signature dough recipe comprised of the original 1974 combination of five carefully curated ingredients, which truly makes their pizza one-of-a-kind. My favorite pizza to order is their signature Great White pizza, which has an olive oil and garlic base and is topped with sun-dried tomatoes, provolone, feta, seasoned ricotta, fresh basil, mozzarella, roma tomatoes, and onions. The atmosphere is very friendly and welcoming, making it a great place to celebrate special occasions or just hang out! If you haven't been here, you should definitely try it and broaden your pizza horizons. I know I'll be going back to it time and time again!</p><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">Mellow Mushroom's "Great White" Pizza and a Pepperoni &amp; Green Pepper Pizza</title><image href="images/mellowmushroompizza.jpg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">Photo of Mellow Mushroom signature "Great White" pizza, as well as another pepperoni and green pepper pizza below it on a tray.</alt></image></fig><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">Inside Mellow Mushroom</title><image href="images/mellowmushroominside.jpg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">Photo of inside Mellow Mushroom restaurant. Showing entrance and where it leads to other parts of the restaurant. Chairs and tables in background.</alt></image></fig></body></topic>